RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
- Series 2. Dance, 1965-1977
  - Dance Companies, Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - O’ Neill Creative Arts in the Classroom (Box 10)
  - Dance Miscellaneous, 1964 - 1975 (Box 11)
    - Connecticut College School of Dance, 1963-1967 (Box 11)
    - Pro-Dance Correspondence (Box 11)
    - Pro-Dance New Haven (Box 11)
    - Pro-Dance Movement Workshop (Box 11)
    - Please Run on the Playground (Misc. Corresp.) (Box 11)
    - Movement Book - Marcia Seigel, editor (Box 11)
    - Mailing list, 1969, September-1971 August (Box 11)
    - Upward Bound - Wooster School, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Exemplary Project, Grant applicant (Box 11)
    - Future (Box 11)
    - Children’s Theatre Showcase, R.E.S.C.U.E., 1968-1969 (Box 11)
    - The Palace Performing Arts Center (Box 12)
    - Performing Artist Associates of New England (Box 12)
    - Pro Dance, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
    - Regional Ballet (Box 12)
    - John D. Rockefeller, III fund (Box 12)
    - Southeastern Connecticut Dance Arts Council, New London (Box 12)
    - Southeastern Connecticut Dance Arts Council, New London (Box 12)
    - Suffield Creative Arts Council, Pat Edwards (Box 12)
    - The Village Assembly (J. Van Cleef) (Box 12)
    - Ethel Walker School (Box 12)
    - Walnut Hill School, Natick, MA (Box 12)
    - West Post Institute for Dance Criticism (Box 12)
    - Wolf Trapp Farm, Vienna, Virginia (Box 12)
    - Junior Women’ s Club (Box 12)
    - Wykham Rise - Gunnery School (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Dance Calendar, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
    - Dance Events in Connecticut, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
    - Project F-6 - Master Classes in Dance (Box 12)
    - Joy Van Cleef - Hartford Lively Arts Festival, 1964 (Box 12)
    - Dance Performance, Project F-1, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Project Suggestion, Dance (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Ballet Company, Grants, 1971 (Box 12)
    - Pro-Dance, Inc., ($2,625), 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - Brookshire Hills Music and Dance Association, Dance in Residence, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Busnell, Lotte Goslar, 1974 June 3-5 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Waterbury Arts Council, Alwin Nikolais (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Waterbury Arts council, Dance Theatre of Harlem, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Bushnell Taylor and Goslar, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Connecticut College Dance Dept., Alvin Ailey, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Connecticut College, Al Ailey, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Smith College Club of Greenwich, Stamford, Alvin Ailey, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Westport P.T.A. Council Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 12)
    - Dance in Residence, Whitby School Parents Association, Paul Taylor (Box 12)
    - Statewide Dance in Residence Tour (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Dance Conferences Program (Box 12)
    - Description Evaluation (Box 12)
    - Application Forms (Box 12)
    - Ballet Etudes Repertory Company, $650 (Box 12)
    - Bowen-Peters Dancers, $650 (Box 12)
    - Conetic Dance Theatre, $325 (Box 12)
    - Confetti Dance Company, $650 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Ballet Company, $325 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Valley Regional Ballet, $650 (Box 12)
    - New England Ballet Theatre, $650 (Box 12)
    - Nutmeg Ballet Company, $650 (Box 12)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, $650 (Box 12)
    - Technical Workshop (F. Grimsey), $200 (Box 12)
    - State Dance Festival, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Albano Youth Ballet of America, $650 (Box 12)
    - Ballet Etudes Repertory Company (Box 12)
    - Conetic Dance Theatre (Box 12)
    - Confetti Dance Theatre, $650 (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Ballet Company (Box 12)
    - Connecticut Valley Regional Ballet, $650 (Box 12)
    - Hartford Ballet, $650 (Box 12)
    - Hartford Ballet, $650 (Box 12)
    - Hartford Conservatory Modern Dance Ensemble, $325 (Box 12)
    - New Haven Dance Center Performing Company, $325 (Box 12)
    - Nutmeg Ballet, $650 (Box 12)
    - New Haven Dance Ensemble (Box 12)
    - New Haven Dance Center Performing Group, $325, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Southern Connecticut State College, $650, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Trinity College Repertory Dances, $325, 1975 (Box 12)
    - American Dance Festival (Box 12)
    - American College Dance Festival Association, New England Region (Box 12)
    - Connecticut College American Dance Festival (Box 12)
  - Dance Movement, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Individual Artist in Field (Box 13)
    - Janet Adler, Film (Box 13)
    - Joseph Albana (Box 13)
    - Jane P. Bampe (Box 13)
    - Ann Barlin (Box 13)
    - Ellen Berland (Box 13)
    - Jane Biral (Box 13)
    - Bonnie Bird (Box 13)
    - Donna Blank (Box 13)
    - Dorothea Buccholz (Box 13)
    - Toni Caiola (Box 13)
    - Myra Copy (Box 13)
    - Verena Chase (Box 13)
    - Linda Chenerton (Box 13)
    - Priscilla Calville (Box 13)
    - Marica Constantine (Box 13)
    - Lyne Conwell (Box 13)
    - Francis Cott (Box 13)
    - Mary Craighill (Box 13)
    - Cherlyl Cutler (Box 13)
    - Norman Dalby (Box 13)
    - Leon Danielian (Box 13)
    - Sharon Dante (Box 13)
    - Avi Davis (Box 13)
    - Emmy Devine (Box 13)
    - Judy Divorin (Box 13)
    - Clyde Evans (Box 13)
    - Gilow, Kinsella, Martin, Film Project (Box 13)
    - Linda S. Fader (Box 13)
    - Jean Fields (Box 13)
    - Cathy Fletcher (Box 13)
    - Sr. Kiernan Foley (Box 13)
    - Kaite Fowle (Box 13)
    - Sheldon Frome (Box 13)
    - Dell Green (Box 13)
    - Kathy Ann Guy (Box 13)
    - Dorothy E. Hafner (Box 13)
    - Beverly Hall (Box 13)
    - Andrea Hancock (Box 13)
    - Marcia S, Heath (Box 13)
    - Doris Hering (Box 13)
    - Jennifer Hill (Box 13)
    - Mildred Hill (Box 13)
    - Lura Hirsch (Box 13)
    - Sue-Chien Hong (Box 13)
    - David Howard (Box 13)
    - Jill Hope Susan Hudson (Box 13)
    - Sachiyo Ito (Box 13)
    - Joanne J. Jacobus (Box 13)
    - Ellen Jacobs (Box 13)
    - Risi Jaraslow (Box 13)
    - Joseph Johnson (Box 13)
    - Estelle Jones (Box 13)
    - Stephanie Jordan (Box 13)
    - Betsy Kagan (Box 13)
    - Joyce Karpiej (Box 13)
    - Beth Kalish (Box 13)
    - Joy Kane (Box 13)
    - Esther Kate (Box 13)
    - Judy Kay (Box 13)
    - Joanne Koab (Box 13)
    - Joseph J. Krakora (Box 13)
    - Barbara Leach (Box 13)
    - Claire Leary (Box 13)
    - Rebecca Leeds (Box 13)
    - Joseph Linsalata (Box 13)
    - Wendy Loomis (Box 13)
    - Jeanne StarrLoeb (Box 13)
    - Adimah Margolis (Box 13)
    - Alice Martin (Box 13)
    - Jean Mead (Box 13)
    - Jean McClaughlin (Box 13)
    - Barbara Mettler (Box 13)
    - Mark Miklavcic (Box 13)
    - Bill Miller Dance Studios (Box 13)
    - Kay Milling (Box 13)
    - Sibley Morosco (Box 13)
    - Patricia Morgan (Box 13)
    - Mirriam Morrison (Box 13)
    - Hilda Mullin (Box 13)
    - Judy Arbitman Murray (Box 13)
    - Edward A. Myers (Box 13)
    - Kathy Papale (Box 13)
    - Wendy Terron (Box 13)
    - Kay Pouraine (Box 13)
    - Kathleen Powers (Box 13)
    - English Public Schools - Drama and Movement Survey - Ms. Reed (Box 13)
    - Jerome Robbins (Box 13)
    - Susan Sandel (Box 13)
    - Walter Schalk (Box 13)
    - Roberta Shalsko (Box 13)
    - Diana Schmitt (Box 13)
    - Claire Schmais (Box 13)
    - Joan Schwartz (Box 13)
    - Jill Anne Silvermann (Box 13)
    - Pamela Smith (Box 13)
    - Janet Soares (Box 13)
    - Betty Sommer (Box 13)
    - Mary Staton (Box 13)
    - Joan Stone (Box 13)
    - Virginia Tanner (Box 13)
    - Ceci Taylor (Box 13)
    - Walter Terry (Box 13)
    - Elizabeth Thompson (Box 13)
    - Helen Townsend (Box 13)
    - Clyde Thompson (Box 13)
    - Joy Van Cleef (Box 13)
    - Robert Winchester (Box 13)
    - Maida Withers (Box 13)
    - Stephanie Woodard (Box 13)
    - Artists, Visiting Artist List, General (Box 13)
    - Movement Education Research - Report on Status in Schools in Connecticut (Box 13)
    - Application - Institute for Movement Exploration (Box 13)
    - The Institute for Movement Exploration, Inc. (Box 13)
    - Dance Therapy - Curriculum Guide (Box 13)
    - Fund for the Improvement of Post-Secondary Education - Fiscal Year 1976 (Box 13)
    - Movement - Curriculum Guide (Box 13)
    - Committee on Research and Dance (Box 13)
  - Dance, 1967 - 1972 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, Complete Report, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, Artists’ Reports, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Danbury, Nilolais Co. & McKayle Co., 1968 (Box 14)
    - Fairfield, McKayle, New Britain and Waterbury, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Hartford, Bushnell - Nikolais and Ailey, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Hartford, Jewish Community Center, McKayle, 1969 (Box 14)
    - New Haven,Nikalais and Paul Taylor, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
    - New Haven, Lewis and American Dance Rep., 1970 (Box 14)
    - New Haven, Nikolais and McKayle, 1969 (Box 14)
    - New London, Nikolais and McKayle, 1968 (Box 14)
    - Storrs, Taylor, 1969 (Box 14)
    - Storrs, Cunningham and Nickolais, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
    - West Hartford, Taylor, 1969 (Box 14)
    - National Endowment Association, Artist-in-Schools (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence Program, Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence Press (Box 14)
    - Storrs, Sanasardo and Taylor, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence - Announcement Letter, 1968-1969 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence - Introductory Letter - Spons., 1968 (Box 14)
    - Report - Pilot, Taylor Performance - Illinois (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, National Endowment Information, 1969-1970 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, National Endowment Information, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence Statistics, 1968-1971 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, Report, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Large Dance Companies Touring Program, NEA (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, Final Reports, 1969-1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, Announcement Letter, 1970 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, Endowment Notice, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, List of Residencies, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, General Information and Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - Dance Companies in Residence, General Information and Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 14)
    - Letters from ASK to Dance Companies (Box 14)
    - “A” through “Z”, 1968-1969-1970 (Box 14)
    - Dance - Address List of Connecticut Dance Teachers (Box 14)
  - Martha Graham Concert, 1966 (Box 15)
    Held at Bushnell, October 1, 1966.
    - Martha Graham Card File (Box 15)
    - Ticket Sales (Box 15)
    - Ticket Pricing (Box 15)
    - Reviews (Box 15)
    - Reports - (CM) (Box 15)
    - Reception (Box 15)
    - Program (Box 15)
    - Promotion (Box 15)
    - Press Material (Box 15)
    - Promotion Committee (Box 15)
    - New Britain list (Box 15)
    - Guests (Box 15)
    - General Strategy (Box 15)
    - Finances (Box 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 15)
    - Contribution Acknowledgement Letter (Box 15)
    - Advertising (Box 15)
    - Martha Graham Grant Application (Box 15)
    - Sponsor list (Box 15)
    - Sponsor acknowledgement form (Box 15)
    - Sponsors, alphabetical by town (Box 15)
    - Ticket Endowment (Box 15)
    - Student ticket (Box 15)
    - Patrons (Box 15)
    - News clippings and other miscellaneous (Box 15)
  - National Dance Companies (Box 49)
    - The ACME Dance Company (Box 49)
    - Luis Agudo Modern Mime (Box 49)
    - Alberts, David (Mime) (Box 49)
    - Albuquerque Dance Theatre (Box 49)
    - Atlanta Contemporary Dance Company (2 folders) (Box 49)
    - The Allnation Company (Box 49)
    - Alvin Ailey American Dance Theatre (New York) (Box 49)
    - American Ballet Theatre (New York) (Box 49)
    - American Dance Company (Formerly Huntington Dance Ensemble) (Box 49)
    - The American Festival Ballet (Box 49)
    - American Folk Ballet (California) (Box 49)
    - Frances Alenikoff and Company (New Jersey) (Box 49)
    - American Ballet Company (New York) (Box 49)
    - American Dance Repertory Company (New York) (Box 49)
    - The American Mime Theatre (New York) (Box 49)
    - Mary Anthony Dance Theatre (New York) (Box 49)
    - Tuki Arkin Mime Theatre (New York) (Box 49)
    - The Atlanta Ballet (Georgia) (Box 49)
    - Asian Theatre Artists (New York) (Box 49)
    - Avital: The Mime of a Thousand Faces (New York) (Box 49)
    - Ayako and Company (New York) (Box 49)
    - Ballet Arts Company (New York) (Box 49)
    - Ballet Concepts (Box 49)
    - Ballet Dance Group (New York) (Box 49)
    - Ballet Del Monte Sol (New Mexico) (Box 49)
    - The Ballet Ensemble of New york (Box 49)
    - Ballet Guild of Cleveland (Ohio) (Box 49)
    - Ballet Hispanico (New York) (Box 49)
    - Ballet La Jeunesse of Los Angeles (California) (Box 49)
    - Ballet Moderno y Folklorico (Guatemala) (Box 49)
    - Ballet Repertory Company (Box 49)
    - Ballet Team (Box 49)
    - Ballet West (2 files) (Box 49)
    - Jose Barrera and his Zambra Flamenca (New York) (Box 49)
    - Batsheval Dance Company of Israel (Box 49)
    - Talley Beatty Dance Company (New York) (Box 49)
    - Bejart Ballet of the 20th Century (Box 49)
    - Bennington College Dance Group (Vermont) (Box 49)
    - Bhaskar and Anjali (Box 49)
    - Bhaskar and Shala (New York) (Box 49)
    - Birmingham Creative Dance Group (Alabama) (Box 49)
    - The Black Ballet –Sally Bowden (Box 49)
    - The Blue Peacock Players (New York) (Box 49)
    - Percival Borde and Company (New York) (Box 49)
    - Gloria Contreras Dance Company (Box 50)
    - Dean Crane Company (New York) - see Ballet Arts Company (Box 50)
    - Merce Cunningham and Dance Company (New York) (Box 50)
    - Cunningham Dance Foundation, Inc. (Box 50)
    - Ruth Currier and Dance Company (Box 50)
    - Russel Curry (Box 50)
    - Dance Adventures (New Jersey) (Box 50)
    - Dance Circle Company of Boston (Massachusetts) (Box 50)
    - Dance Repertory Company (Box 50)
    - Dancers Studio (New York) (Box 50)
    - Dance Theatre of North Carolina (Box 50)
    - Dance Theatre Workshop (New York) (Box 50)
    - Dances of India (Bhaskar)
    - Dances of Two Worlds (Box 50)
    - Dance Theatre of Harlem (Box 50)
    - Dances We Dance (New York) (Box 50)
    - Dancers Workshop Company (California) (Box 50)
    - Danzas Venezuela (New York) (Box 50)
    - The Chuck Davis Dance Company (Box 50)
    - Dayton Civic Ballet Company (Ohio) (Box 50)
    - Carmen De LaVallade’s American Dance (New York) (Box 50)
    - Demille, Agnes and the Heritage Ballet (Box 50)
    - Des Moines Civic Ballet Company (Iowa) (Box 50)
    - Jean Leon Destine and His Haitian Dance Company (New York) (Box 50)
    - Ritha Devi Danes of India (Box 50)
    - Dinizulu Agrican Dancers (New York) (Box 50)
    - Directional Concepts Dance Theatre Foundation (Richard Brown) (Box 50)
    - Discovery Dance Group (Texas) (Box 50)
    - “East Meets West Through Dance” (New York) (Box 50)
    - Eglevsky Ballet Company of Long Island (Box 50)
    - Elmira-Corning Ballet Company, Inc. (New York) (Box 50)
    - Erdman, Jean (Box 50)
    - Erie Civic Ballet Company (Box 50)
    - Ethnic Dance Arts, Inc. (Box 50)
    - Expression of Two Arts (New York) (Box 50)
    - Fairmount Dance Theatre (Box 50)
    - Faison, The George (Universal Dance Experience) (Box 50)
    - Louis Falco and Company of Featured Dancers (New York) (Box 50)
    - The Viola Farber Dance Company (Box 50)
    - Festival Dance Company (Massachusetts) (Box 50)
    - Fiesta Mexicana (Box 50)
    - 5 by 2 Dance Company (Box 50)
    - First Chamber Dance Quartet (Box 50)
    - Flamenco in Concert (California) (Box 50)
    - Boston Ballet Company, Inc. (Massachusetts) (Box 50)
    - Brianski Ballet Company (New York) (Box 50)
    - Brockport Resident Dance Company (Box 50)
    - Jane Brown (Box 50)
    - Brown, Trisha (Box 50)
    - The Chamber Ballet - Resident Ballet of the University of Akron (Box 50)
    - Charlottesville Civic Ballet Company (Virginia) (Box 50)
    - Chicago Contemporary Dance Theatre (Illinois) (Box 50)
    - Nadia Chilkousky Nahumck (Box 50)
    - Choreographer’s Theatre (2 files) (Box 50)
    - The Cincinnati Ballet Company (Box 50)
    - Clark Center Joffrey Baller (Box 50)
    - The Cubibulo (Box 50)
    - Classics from other Lands (New York) (Box 50)
    - Ze-eva Cohen (solo recital) (New York) (Box 50)
    - Colleen Corkre Dance Company (New York) (Box 50)
    - Composers and Choreographer’s Theatre, Inc. (Box 50)
    - Concert Ballet Group of Tacoma (Washington) (Box 50)
    - Alice Condodina and Dance Company (New York) (Box 50)
    - Idla Ensemble (Box 51)
    - Inbal Dance Theatre (Box 51)
    - Indo-American Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Sachiyo Ito (Box 51)
    - Indrani (Box 51)
    - Indra-Nila Performs Dances of South India (New York) (Box 51)
    - Judith Jaacobs (Box 51)
    - The Jacob’s Pillow School and Festival (Box 51)
    - Judith Janus (New York) (Box 51)
    - Elle Johnson Dance Company (California) (Box 51)
    - Johnson, Raymond (Box 51)
    - Louis Johnson Dance Theatre (Box 51)
    - Judy Joseph and Ken Brelsfoard (Illinois) (Box 51)
    - Katha Kali Dance Theatre from India (Box 51)
    - Kaleidoscope - a Company for All Dance (New York) (Box 51)
    - Zwi Kanar - Pantomime Artists (Belgium) (Box 51)
    - Katayen Dance Theatre, Inc. (New York) (Box 51)
    - Keen, Elizabeth Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Keuter, Cliff (Box 51)
    - King Bruce (Box 51)
    - Claude Kipnis (Israeli Mime Theatre) (Box 51)
    - Hara Kohav Dance Company (New York) (Box 51)
    - Pauline Koner Dance Company (Box 51)
    - La Mariquita (California) (Box 51)
    - Lalli (Dances of India) (Box 51)
    - Lamhut, Phyliss Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Lang, Pearl and Dance Company (Box 51)
    - The Laubins (Wyoming) (Box 51)
    - The Lecture - Concert Trio (Box 51)
    - Les Grandes Ballets Canadiens (Canada) (Box 51)
    - Le groupe do la Place Royal (Canada) (Box 51)
    - Les Ballets Trockadero de Monte Carlo (Box 51)
    - Bella Lewitsky Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Jose Limon Dance Company (New York) (Box 51)
    - Gertrude Lippincott (Minnesota) (Box 51)
    - Merle Lister Dance Company (New York) (Box 51)
    - Katherine Litz with Company (Box 51)
    - Murray Louis Dance Company (New York) (Box 51)
    - Louis - Nikolais Dance Theatre (Box 51)
    - Louisville Ballet Repertory Company (Box 51)
    - Luigi’s Jazz Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Luise Ballet Flamenco Company (Box 51)
    - Macri -Weil Sicilim Theatre (Box 51)
    - Mainelli, Louis G. (Box 51)
    - Manjusri Indian Dances (Box 51)
    - Manhattan Festival Ballet (Box 51)
    - Fort Worth Ballet (Fort Worth) (Box 51)
    - Emily Frankel (Box 51)
    - Fusion (Box 51)
    - Irene Gabriel Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Gamson, Annabelle (Box 51)
    - Mimi Garrard Dance Company, Inc. (Box 51)
    - Georgetown Workshop (Washington, D.C.) (Box 51)
    - The Gus Giordano Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Gleanlings (New York) (Box 51)
    - Lotte Goslar Pantomime Circus (Box 51)
    - Carola Goya and Matteo (Box 51)
    - Martha Graham Dance Company (Box 51)
    - The Grand Union (Yvonne Rainer) (Box 51)
    - Jose Greco (Box 51)
    - Salvatore Guida (Box 51)
    - Paschal Guzman/Downtown Ballet (Box 51)
    - Nora Guthrie and Ted Rotante (Box 51)
    - Hadarim - Israeli Song and Dance Theatre (California) (Box 51)
    - Arthua Hall’s Afro American Dance Ensemble (Box 51)
    - Halprin, Ann Dancer’s workshop Theatre (Box 51)
    - Harkness Ballet (Box 51)
    - Harkness Youth Dancers (Box 51)
    - Harry (Box 51)
    - Nancy Hauser Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Hayden, Melissa (Box 51)
    - Eric Hawkins Dance Company (Box 51)
    - Deborah Hay (Box 51)
    - Heart Beat of Africa Troupe (Box 51)
    - High School of Performing Arts (New York) (Box 51)
    - Hillyer, Kazuko International, Inc. (Box 51)
    - Wendy Hilton (Box 51)
    - Hodson Management (Box 51)
    - Lucas Hoving Dance Company (New York) (Box 51)
    - Houston Ballet Company (Box 51)
    - Howard, Mel Productions, Inc. (Box 51)
    - Flower Hujer Dance Theatre (Box 51)
    - Alwyn Nikolais Dance Theatre (Box 52)
    - Martha Nishitani Modern Dance Company (Washington) (Box 52)
    - North Carolina Dance Theatre (Box 52)
    - Northern Westchester Dance Company (New York) (Box 52)
    - Oregon Ballet Classique (Oregon) (Box 52)
    - Oukhtomsky, Valentina Dramatic Dance Ensemble (Box 52)
    - Ohio Chamber Ballet (Box 52)
    - Pacific Ballet (California) (Box 52)
    - Pacific Dance Theater (California) (Box 52)
    - Pact Ballet Company (South Africa) (Box 52)
    - Ruth Page’s International Ballet (Illinois) (Box 52)
    - The Paper Bag Players, Inc. (New York) (Box 52)
    - Mariano Parra Ballet Espanol (New York) (Box 52)
    - Pasadena Dance Theatre (California) (Box 52)
    - Ricardo Peinado Y su Ballet Jarocho (California) (Box 52)
    - Stanze Peterson Dance Theatre, Inc. (Box 52)
    - Pennsylvania Ballet Company (Box 52)
    - Rudy Perez Dance Theatre Company (Box 52)
    - Pilobolus (Box 52)
    - Phakavali (Box 52)
    - Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre (Box 52)
    - Poetry - In - Dance (Washington, D.C.) (Box 52)
    - Eleo Pomare Dance Company (Box 52)
    - Premiere Dance Arts Company (Colorado) (Box 52)
    - Puerto Rican Dance Theatre Inc. (Box 52)
    - Rainer, Yvonne (Box 52)
    - The Tina Ramirez Dancers (New York) (Box 52)
    - Shanta Rao (Box 52)
    - Kay Raphael (New York) (Box 52)
    - Lilian Shapero Dance Company (New York) (Box 52)
    - Sally Ray International Dancer (New York) (Box 52)
    - Don Redlich Dance Company (New York) (Box 52)
    - Repertory Dance Theatre (Utah) (Box 52)
    - Repertory Dancers of New Jersey (Box 52)
    - Rhode Island Dance Repertory Company (Box 52)
    - Larry Richardson and Dance Company (Box 52)
    - Ririe - Woodbury Dance Company University of Utah (Box 52)
    - Alonzo Rivera (Box 52)
    - Rivera, Luis Spanksh Dance Company (Box 52)
    - Dyann Robinson & Mike Malone (Washington D.C.) (Box 52)
    - Barbara Roan Danceworks Irene Feigenheimer (Box 52)
    - Rod Rodgers (Box 52)
    - Roxanne (Risa Jaraslow and Wendy Perron) (Box 52)
    - Paul Sanasardo Dance Company (New York) (Box 52)
    - San Diego Repertory Jazz Dance Company (San Diego) (Box 52)
    - Rose, Phyliss Dance Company (Box 52)
    - Mara - see Classics from Other Lands (Box 52)
    - Sophie Maslow Dance Company (New York) (Box 52)
    - Mata and Hari (New York) (Box 52)
    - Mario Maya (New York) (Box 52)
    - Helen McGehee (New York) (Box 52)
    - Matteo and the Indo-American Dance Company (Box 52)
    - Donald McKayle (Box 52)
    - Mime (Box 52)
    - Merdedith Monk and the House (Box 52)
    - Merry - Go - Rounders (New Jersey) (Box 52)
    - Metropolitan Opera Ballet (Box 52)
    - Joan Miller Chamber Arts / Dance Players (Box 52)
    - Minnesota Dance Theatre (Box 52)
    - Minnesota Dance Theatre and School (2 files) (Box 52)
    - The Mohan Dev Company (California) (Box 52)
    - Jose Molina Bailes Espanoles (New York) (Box 52)
    - Tony Montanaro, Mime (New York) (Box 52)
    - Irina Monter (California) (Box 52)
    - Loal Montes and Her Spanish Dancers (California) (Box 52)
    - Morca and La Conte (Flamenco in Concert) (Box 52)
    - Munt Brooks Dance Studio (Box 52)
    - Seamus Murphy Dance Company (Box 52)
    - Nagrin, Daniel (New York) (Box 52)
    - Nala Najan and Anurdha (New Jersey) (Box 52)
    - National Ballet of Canada (Ontario, Canada) (Box 52)
    - The National Ballet (Washington) (Box 52)
    - Newburgh Ballet Guild, Inc. (New York) (Box 52)
    - New England Dance Theatre, Inc. (Box 52)
    - New England Dinosaur (2 files) (Box 52)
    - Gloria Newman Dance Company (California ) (Box 52)